▍2026 华盛顿 WTA500 决赛
伊埃拉 4-6 6-4 6-0 佩古拉 · 赛后亚军致辞
Thank you everyone.
谢谢大家
Well, first I want to congratulate Alex
首先我想恭喜伊埃拉
on an amazing week,
这一周打得太出色了
an amazing tournament.
整站都很出色
I don't know I I don't know how much more
我不知道还能再说什么
I can say, but you're an amazing player
但你是个了不起的球员
and just to see how far you've come
看你这两年走了多远
over the last couple years
从我们第一次交手
when we first played,
到今天
to see the amazing fans
还有那些球迷
that follow you every single place you go.
你走到哪儿他们跟到哪儿
It's not fun to play
跟你打起来
against, but I do appreciate
是不好受 但我真的很享受
the really fun atmosphere.
那个气氛
I do. I think it's amazing, so congrats.
真的 我觉得很棒 恭喜你
All the best to you and your team
祝你和你的团队
and your coach.
还有你的教练一切都好
I would like to go ahead
我想谢谢
and thank my coach
我的教练
and my hitting partner Mark and Spencer
和陪练 马克和斯宾塞
that were here with me this week.
这一周一直陪着我
My other coach Mark who's not here,
还有没来的另一位教练马克
my coach
我的教练
or my trainer John who's also not here,
或者说体能师约翰 他也没来
but thanks you guys
谢谢你们
for continuously always putting in the work
一周又一周
with me week after week and you know,
一直陪我一起下功夫
unfortunate today, but you know,
今天有点遗憾 不过
we've been playing some great tennis
我们这阵子打得很好
and just thanks so much for all you guys
谢谢你们为我做的一切
do for me and I really appreciate it.
我真的很感激
I would like to thank Mubadala for putting
我想谢谢穆巴达拉
on this event also along with Mark, Danny,
办了这项赛事 还有马克 丹尼
Christina, everyone else that helps.
克里斯蒂娜 和所有帮忙的人
I've seen you guys most of you guys
你们中大多数人
since I first won this title here in 2019
2019 年我首次夺冠时就见过
and I love coming back
我特别喜欢回到这儿
and seeing the same volunteers,
还是同一批志愿者
the same locker room attendants,
同一批更衣室的人
the same people
餐厅里的服务员
in dining like it's the same people
也还是同一批
and you guys remember me
而你们还记得我
from when I first came here, so I always
记得我第一次来的时候
have the best feeling coming back.
所以每次回来都特别舒服
It's it's always feels super special
每次都觉得很特别
and so much has happened obviously
从我上次夺冠到今天
since the last time I won this title and it still
显然发生了很多事
feels just as special coming back here.
但回来的感觉一样特别
So everyone on the grounds,
所以场地里的每一个人
all the volunteers are amazing.
志愿者们都太好了
You guys are so friendly, so nice,
你们又友善又热情
the security, the ball kids, everybody
安保 球童 每一个
that helps put this on and I know it
帮着把这项赛事办起来的人
was not an easy feat to move this final
我知道把决赛挪到周一
to a Monday final.
一点都不容易
Unfortunately,
很遗憾
the weather yesterday was not very good
昨天的天气
to us, but thank you guys so much
对我们不太友好 但太谢谢你们
for just for being here for an extra day,
谢谢你们多留了一天
for putting this event on for an extra day,
多办了一天
for working an extra day.
多上了一天班
I'm sure hopefully you're getting paid
希望你们
a little overtime for that, but everyone
拿到了加班费 而且每个人
is here bright and early this morning ready
今天一大早就来了
to go, and um I know that it was not easy
我知道这不容易
and it was a hard decision,
那是个很难的决定
but thank you guys for doing what was best
但谢谢你们做了
for the players yesterday.
对球员最好的选择
Thanks Mark for being able to make
谢谢马克
that decision,
拍了这个板
and we were able to come out here
让我们今天能上场
and have an amazing final.
打了一场很棒的决赛
And last but not least, thanks to the crowd.
最后 谢谢现场的观众
Like Mark said,
就像马克说的那样
I I can definitely confirm probably
我可以确认
for a Monday final, this is this is the best
这大概是我见过最好的一届
Monday final crowd I've I've seen.
周一决赛观众
I know I'm sure uh
我知道
some people took off took off work.
有些人是请了假的
I won't tell them
我不会告诉他们
where you guys were, but um it's amazing
你们跑哪儿去了 但你们能来
that you guys showed up, and again even
真的太好了 还有
to to all the Filipino fans that came out
所有到场的菲律宾球迷
and have supported Uh you guys
谢谢你们的支持
are still helping grow tennis around
你们在帮着网球
the world, and I appreciate
在全世界成长
that being a you know,
而作为一名女运动员
a female athlete being in tennis.
我很感激这件事
We love to see that grow,
我们特别希望看到它长大
so thanks so much everyone.
所以非常感谢大家